{
   "response_code":0,
   "results":[
      {
         "category":"Animals",
         "type":"multiple",
         "difficulty":"medium",
         "question":"What%20type%20of%20animal%20is%20a%20natterjack%3F",
         "correct_answer":"Toad",
         "incorrect_answers":[
            "Bird",
            "Fish",
            "Insect"
         ]
      },
      {
         "category":"Geography",
         "type":"multiple",
         "difficulty":"medium",
         "question":"How%20many%20sovereign%20states%20are%20members%20of%20the%20United%20Nations%3F",
         "correct_answer":"195",
         "incorrect_answers":[
            "201",
            "153",
            "178"
         ]
      },
      {
         "category":"History",
         "type":"multiple",
         "difficulty":"medium",
         "question":"Who%20was%20the%20first%20explorer%20to%20sail%20to%20North%20America%3F",
         "correct_answer":"Leif%20Erikson",
         "incorrect_answers":[
            "Christopher%20Columbus",
            "Amerigo%20Vespucci",
            "Ferdinand%20Magellan"
         ]
      },
      {
         "category":"Entertainment%3A%20Film",
         "type":"multiple",
         "difficulty":"medium",
         "question":"In%20which%201955%20film%20does%20Frank%20Sinatra%20play%20Nathan%20Detroit%3F",
         "correct_answer":"Guys%20and%20Dolls",
         "incorrect_answers":[
            "Anchors%20Aweigh",
            "From%20Here%20to%20Eternity",
            "High%20Society"
         ]
      },
      {
         "category":"Entertainment%3A%20Music",
         "type":"multiple",
         "difficulty":"medium",
         "question":"Which%20Beatle%20led%20the%20way%20across%20the%20zebra%20crossing%20on%20the%20Abbey%20Road%20album%20cover%3F",
         "correct_answer":"John",
         "incorrect_answers":[
            "Paul",
            "George",
            "Ringo"
         ]
      },
      {
         "category":"Entertainment%3A%20Television",
         "type":"multiple",
         "difficulty":"medium",
         "question":"What%20is%20the%20setting%20of%20the%20show%20%22Parks%20and%20Recreation%22%3F",
         "correct_answer":"Pawnee%2C%20Indiana",
         "incorrect_answers":[
            "Eagleton%2C%20Indiana",
            "Pasadena%2C%20California",
            "London%2C%20England"
         ]
      },
      {
         "category":"Geography",
         "type":"multiple",
         "difficulty":"medium",
         "question":"What%20African%20country%20has%20Portuguese%20as%20its%20official%20language%3F",
         "correct_answer":"Mozambique",
         "incorrect_answers":[
            "Botswana",
            "Gabon",
            "Togo"
         ]
      },
      {
         "category":"Politics",
         "type":"multiple",
         "difficulty":"medium",
         "question":"The%202014%20movie%20%22The%20Raid%202%3A%20Berandal%22%20was%20mainly%20filmed%20in%20which%20Asian%20country%3F",
         "correct_answer":"Indonesia",
         "incorrect_answers":[
            "Thailand",
            "Brunei",
            "Malaysia"
         ]
      },
      {
         "category":"Entertainment%3A%20Musicals%20%26%20Theatres",
         "type":"multiple",
         "difficulty":"medium",
         "question":"What%20play%20is%20the%20quote%20%22Hell%20is%20other%20people%22%20from%3F",
         "correct_answer":"No%20Exit",
         "incorrect_answers":[
            "The%20Devil%20and%20the%20Good%20Lord",
            "The%20Condemned%20of%20Altona",
            "The%20Flies"
         ]
      },
      {
         "category":"History",
         "type":"multiple",
         "difficulty":"medium",
         "question":"What%20is%20the%20bloodiest%20event%20in%20United%20States%20history%2C%20in%20terms%20of%20casualties%3F",
         "correct_answer":"Battle%20of%20Antietam",
         "incorrect_answers":[
            "Pearl%20Harbor",
            "September%2011th",
            "D-Day"
         ]
      },
      {
         "category":"History",
         "type":"multiple",
         "difficulty":"medium",
         "question":"What%20was%20Genghis%20Khan%27s%20real%20name%3F",
         "correct_answer":"Tem%C3%BCjin",
         "incorrect_answers":[
            "M%C3%B6ngke",
            "%C3%96gedei",
            "Tem%C3%BCr"
         ]
      },
      {
         "category":"Entertainment%3A%20Books",
         "type":"multiple",
         "difficulty":"medium",
         "question":"In%20the%20%22Harry%20Potter%22%20novels%2C%20what%20must%20a%20Hogwarts%20student%20do%20to%20enter%20the%20Ravenclaw%20Common%20Room%3F",
         "correct_answer":"Answer%20a%20riddle",
         "incorrect_answers":[
            "Rhythmically%20tap%20barrels%20with%20a%20wand",
            "Speak%20a%20password",
            "Knock%20in%20sequence"
         ]
      },
      {
         "category":"Entertainment%3A%20Film",
         "type":"multiple",
         "difficulty":"medium",
         "question":"Who%20directed%20the%20movie%20%22Alien%22%3F",
         "correct_answer":"Ridley%20Scott",
         "incorrect_answers":[
            "Christopher%20Nolan",
            "Michael%20Bay",
            "James%20Cameron"
         ]
      },
      {
         "category":"Entertainment%3A%20Books",
         "type":"multiple",
         "difficulty":"medium",
         "question":"Which%20of%20the%20following%20was%20the%20author%20of%20%22Username%20Evie%22%3F",
         "correct_answer":"Joe%20Sugg",
         "incorrect_answers":[
            "Zoe%20Sugg",
            "Joe%20Weller",
            "Alfie%20Deyes"
         ]
      },
      {
         "category":"Entertainment%3A%20Japanese%20Anime%20%26%20Manga",
         "type":"multiple",
         "difficulty":"medium",
         "question":"In%20the%20%22Re%3AZero%22%20manga%20series%2C%20which%20of%20the%20following%20Sin%20Archbishops%20eats%20Rem%27s%20existence%3F",
         "correct_answer":"Ley%20Batenkaitos",
         "incorrect_answers":[
            "Roy%20Alphard",
            "Petelgeuse%20Romanee-Conti",
            "Louis%20Arneb"
         ]
      },
      {
         "category":"History",
         "type":"multiple",
         "difficulty":"medium",
         "question":"What%20year%20did%20Skoal%2C%20a%20smokeless%20Tobacco%20company%2C%20release%20their%20first%20line%20of%20Pouches%2C%20known%20as%20%22Skoal%20Bandits%22%3F",
         "correct_answer":"1983",
         "incorrect_answers":[
            "1934",
            "1984",
            "1822"
         ]
      },
      {
         "category":"Entertainment%3A%20Comics",
         "type":"multiple",
         "difficulty":"medium",
         "question":"In%20Calvin%20and%20Hobbes%2C%20what%20is%20the%20name%20of%20the%20babysitter%27s%20boyfriend%3F",
         "correct_answer":"Charlie",
         "incorrect_answers":[
            "Dave",
            "Charles",
            "Nathaniel"
         ]
      },
      {
         "category":"Entertainment%3A%20Japanese%20Anime%20%26%20Manga",
         "type":"multiple",
         "difficulty":"medium",
         "question":"Which%20of%20these%20is%20not%20a%20world%20in%20the%20anime%20%22Buddyfight%22%3F",
         "correct_answer":"Ancient%20Dragon%20World",
         "incorrect_answers":[
            "Dragon%20World",
            "Star%20Dragon%20World",
            "Darkness%20Dragon%20World"
         ]
      },
      {
         "category":"Art",
         "type":"multiple",
         "difficulty":"medium",
         "question":"Who%20painted%20the%20epic%20mural%20Guernica%3F",
         "correct_answer":"Pablo%20Picasso",
         "incorrect_answers":[
            "Francisco%20Goya",
            "Leonardo%20da%20Vinci",
            "Henri%20Matisse"
         ]
      },
      {
         "category":"Entertainment%3A%20Comics",
         "type":"multiple",
         "difficulty":"medium",
         "question":"In%20the%20Hellboy%20universe%2C%20who%20founded%20the%20BPRD%3F",
         "correct_answer":"Trevor%20Bruttenholm",
         "incorrect_answers":[
            "Kate%20Corrigan",
            "Johann%20Kraus",
            "Benjamin%20Daimio"
         ]
      }
   ]
}